

VIKTOR TAKÁCS

My Contact

★ takacsv90@gmail.com

(+36209820666

4027, Debrecen

Viktor Takács Portfolio

Hard Skill

- Proficient in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Familiarity with JavaScript frameworks like React
- · Version control systems like Git
- Responsive web design and crossbrowser compatibility
- Expertise in accessibility principles and practices

Soft Skill

- Effective communication
- Analytical problem-solving
- Creativity
- Attention to detail
- Adapt to new technologies
- Passion for web development

Education Background

- University of Debrecen
 Masters in Marketing
 Completed in 2024
- University of Debrecen
 Degree in Economics
 Completed in 2022
- Udemy & Other Certificates

Completed comprehensive online courses in React, Redux, and TypeScript from Udemy and Web Dev Simplified, enhancing my skills in front-end web development.

Completed in 2023

About Me

Actively involved in self-directed web development, I specialize in crafting intricate applications with expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, and React and Redux Toolkit. My unwavering dedication to continuous learning fuels my passion for tackling new challenges in the ever-evolving field of web development.

Professional Experience

P&M Solutions | Frontend Developer 2023 - Present

- Skilled in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, and Redux Toolkit
- Developed and implemented numerous websites and applications using ReactJS
- Utilized problem-solving and analytical skills to identify and resolve complex technical issues
- Excelled in communication and collaboration with team members

webwise Hungary Kft | Customer Succes Manager 2022 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Build and maintain strong customer relationships
- Drive customer satisfaction and retention
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams
- Identify and cross-sell additional products and services
- Maintain accurate customer data and records

Gazdafi Electronic Kft | Marketing Assistant Intern 2021 – 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Conducted market research and analyzed data to inform marketing strategies
- Created and produced a variety of marketing materials
- Assisted with sales and customer support initiatives

Magyar Telekom Nyrt | Help Dest 2020 – 2021

Key responsibilities:

- · Provided technical support to customers
- Troubleshoot issues
- Provided product info
- Managed customer relationships, maintain knowledge base, and install/configure hardware/software.